Curriculum Vitae



Personal Info:

Name and Surname: ALEXE BOGDAN

Date and Place of birth: 07.08.1992(Age 27)BUCHAREST, ROMANIA

Nationality: Romanian

Full Address:street:PANTELIMON NR.359,BUCHAREST,ROMANIA

Mob tel.:0721406009

e-mail:BOGDAN 19922015@yahoo.com

Skype login:

Travel Passport:ROMANIAN
C1/D American visa:

Foreign Languages - ENGLISH/INTERMEDIAR

English -beginner/ intermediate/fluent (chose the right level)

Other languages: beginner/ intermediate/fluent (chose the right level)

Education:

Employment History:

Period (month, year, from-to)10DECEMBER2012-14MAY2014

Position: WAITER

Company's name City/Country:CERVO/BUCHAREST/ROMANIA Duties: CUSTOMERS SERVICE, SETUP, CLEANING ... ETC.

Reason of leaving: A BETTER WORKPLACE

Period (month, year):28AUGUST2014-20FEBRUARY2015

Position:BARISTA

Company's name City/Country:GIORGIO S" BUCHAREST/ROMANIA Duties:MADE COFFEE, CLEANING, CHECKOUT , GOODS ORDERS AND SETUP

Reason of leaving: A BETTER WORKPLACE

Period (month, year):23FERBUARY2015-UNTIL THE PRESENT 12.01.2020

Position :BARISTA

Company's name City/Country:IDEALL COFFEE BUCHAREST/ROMANIA

Duties: MEDE COFFEE, SETUP, CHECKOUT, GOODS ORDERS, CLEANING ETC.

Reason of leaving:

I AM STILL HERE !

PROFILE:

I LIKE WORKING , LEARNING NEW THINGS AND HAVING THE BEST EXPERIENCES . I LOVE TO BE POSITIVE , AND TO BECOME AN EXAMPLE TO FOLLOW .

Very customer focused and with high standards at all times, with an enthusiastic and ambitious attitude, high volume .

KEY SKILLS

I HAVE THE ABILITY TO COME WITHE THE IDEAS FOR A GOOD AND SINGLE CUSTOMER SATISFACTION .

CAREER HISTORY
BARISTA
AUGUST2014-JANUAR2020

WORK IN COFFEE Responsibilities:

EVERY TIME I ENSURE THAT I HAVE THE FUNCTIONAL EXPRESSOR.

- I CHECK ALL THE STOCK TIME, AND GIVES ORDERS IN TIME.
- I WELCOME THE CUSTOMERS, WITH THE SMILE ON THE LIPS, AND I TRY TO

PERSONALIZE THE COFFEE, ACCORDING TO THE CUSTOMER PERSONALITY.

- I treat my clients like my own friends, and I try to interact more with them.
- I AM ALL THE TIME ATTENTION TO THE INFORMATION, ABOUT THE COFFEE AND I TRY TO PERFECT MORE.

AT THE END OF THE DAYS I CHECK THE MARKET HOUSE, AND I MAKE SURE I HAVE NO LOSSES.

CLEANING THE EXPRESSOR AND CLEANING AT THE WORK REPRESENTS THE END OF A DAY IN THE BAR.

Achievements:

Good customer skills, in charge for the bar, inventory, cleaning, sales, record keeping.

Education

GENERAL SCHOOL 1999-2007-LUCIAN BLAGA
HIGH SCHOOL2007-2012-GR.SC.IND.SFANTUL PANTELIMON

Leisure Activities:

music, movies AND Football .